<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>Evergreen Betas</title>
        <link>https://ranchero.com/downloads/evergreen-beta.xml</link>
        <description>Most recent Evergreen changes with links to updates.</description>
        <language>en</language>

		<item>
          <title>Evergreen 1.0d40</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
            <p>Improve font sizing in the timeline.</p>
            <p>Show no-selection or multiple-selection text in the detail view when appropriate.</p>
            <p>Give the source list an almost-white background (96%) instead of using the blueish blur view. Reason: favicons are often created with the expectation that they will be placed on a white background — they often don’t include transparency. They end up looking better on this almost-white background.</p>
 							 							 						
    						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 22:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d40.zip" sparkle:version="1040" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d40" length="7357549" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

		<item>
          <title>Evergreen 1.0d39</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
 							<h4>Timeline</h4>
 							<p>Moved avatars and feed icons to the right.</p>
 							<p>Tweaked some colors and margins.</p>
 							<p>Removed the grid line.</p>
 							<p>Made the text for no-title articles darker.</p>
 							 							 						
    						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d39.zip" sparkle:version="1034" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d39" length="7351715" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

		<item>
          <title>Evergreen 1.0d38</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
 							<h4>Starring</h4>
 							<p>You can mark articles starred and unstarred — via the menu, contextual menu in the timeline, and toolbar button.</p>
 							<p>The Starred smart feed shows all your starred articles. Tip: cmd-3 takes you to the Starred feed.</p>
 							
 							<h4>Misc.</h4>
 							<p>Added special cases to the JSON Feed parser for known feeds that put HTML entities in article titles. (Kottke, Pixel Envy.)</p>
 							<p>Revised the JSON parser feed detector to allow for a version property that uses the incorrect scheme. (Makes Pixel Envy’s feed work.)</p>
 							<p>Made Kottke’s feed a default for new users.</p> 							 						
    						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 12:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d38.zip" sparkle:version="1027" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d38" length="7349333" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

		<item>
          <title>Evergreen 1.0d37</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
 							<h4>Misc.</h4>
 							<p>Make the Copy command work in the sidebar and timeline.</p>
 							<p>Add Donate to App Camp for Girls item to the Help menu. The Help menu is now a place where <i>you</i> can help.</p>
 							<p>When selecting multiple items in the sidebar, show articles in the timeline from the entire selection, not just from one thing.</p>
 							<p>Update folder unread count when a feed it contains is deleted.</p>
 							<p>Update copyright date in About box.</p>
 							<p>Disallow blurring behind the title bar, since it’s buggy.</p>
 							<p>Don’t clear undo stack when sidebar changes selection.</p>
 							<p>Remember Feed Directory’s window frame between runs.</p>
 							
 							<h4>Puntings</h4>
 							<p>Font size is punted till after 1.0, and its preferences have been removed until then.</p>
 							<p>Feed Directory is simplified — the feed preview feature has been punted till after 1.0.</p>
 							 						
    						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 13:25:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d37.zip" sparkle:version="981" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d37" length="7374447" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

		<item>
          <title>Evergreen 1.0d36</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
            <h4>AppleScript!</h4>
            <p>Evergreen is scriptable — use Script Editor to see the app’s scripting dictionary.</p>

						<h4>Sidebar</h4>
						<p>Fetch and display articles for smart feeds. (The Starred feed is empty for now, though, because you can’t actually star anything yet.)</p>
						<p>Display a contextual menu for feeds, folders, and smart feeds.</p>
						
						<h4>Timeline</h4>
						<p>Display a contextual menu for articles.</p>
						
						<h4>Detail</h4>
						<p>Remove contextual menu items from the web view that don’t make sense for Evergren — Reload, for example.</p>
						            
            <h4>Misc.</h4>
            <p>Rearrange the default toolbar to put Search in the middle.</p>
 						<p>Update the name of the Show/Hide Sidebar menu command when needed.</p>
 						
    						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 14:35:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d36.zip" sparkle:version="959" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d36" length="8813422" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

		<item>
          <title>Evergreen 1.0d35</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
            <h4>Sidebar Gear Menu</h4>
            <p>You can rename, mark as read, and copy URLs.</p>
            <p>(Delete isn’t there yet, but it’s planned for 1.0.)</p>
            
            <h4>Misc.</h4>
            <p>You can sort the timeline by newest on top or oldest on top. See the View > Sort By menu.</p>
            <p>Share menu now supports EagleFiler Impot and Add to Reading List. (Thanks to a contribution by Michael Tsai.)</p>
            <p>Go > Today, Unread, Starred commands work, including keyboard shortcuts. (Nothing appears yet, though. That’s a separate bug.)</p>
            <p>Fixed a bug where the add-feed command wouldn’t disable when a sheet was already displaying.</p>
            <p>Removed Debug menu when running a Release build.</p>
            <p>Punted multiple window support till after 1.0.</p>

    						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d35.zip" sparkle:version="920" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d35" length="7331028" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

			<item>
          <title>Evergreen 1.0d34</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
            <h4>Icons</h4>
            <p>Updated app icon — tree redrawn to make branches wider and have definition.</p>
            <p>Updated next unread icon to fit better.</p>
            <p>(Icons are by Brad Ellis.)</p>
            
            <h4>Inspector</h4>
            <p>Window > Info, or cmd-I, opens the Inspector. You can change the names of feeds and folders. You can get the home page URL and feed URL of a feed (which is pretty important when filing a bug for a feed).</p>

            <h4>Misc.</h4>
            <p>Reload the timeline when a feed updates (when feed is selected, or when a folder containing the feed is selected).</p>

    						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d34.zip" sparkle:version="852" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d34" length="7455712" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

			<item>
          <title>Evergreen 1.0d33</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
            <h4>Send to MarsEdit</h4>
            <p>If you have <a href="https://red-sweater.com/marsedit/">MarsEdit</a> on your Mac, then you can send an article from Evergreen to MarsEdit via the sharing menu in the toolbar.</p>
            <p>In MarsEdit you can edit the post and add your commentary before posting to your blog.</p>
    
    						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 14:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d33.zip" sparkle:version="813" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d33" length="7274707" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

				<item>
          <title>Evergreen 1.0d32</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
            <h4>Send to Micro.blog</h4>
            <p>See the Sharing command in the toolbar for a new feature: send to Micro.blog. This sends the current item to your copy of the Micro.blog Mac app (if you have it). It gets launched if necessary. You can edit the post in Micro.blog before actually posting it to your microblog.</p>
            <p>This is hugely important, because feed reading isn’t just about reading — it’s also about posting. While Evergreen doesn’t itself include a way to post to the web, other apps do, and Evergreen should make it easy to connect to these other apps.</p>
            <p>Note: send-to-MarsEdit is next, probably in the next release.</p>
            
            <h4>Misc.</h4>
            <p>Improve the promptness and reliability of feed icons and favicons appearing in the timeline (when a folder is selected).</p>
            <p>Increase the indentation in the source list so that feeds inside folders line up better.</p>
   
    						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d32.zip" sparkle:version="804" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d32" length="7265605" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

				<item>
          <title>Version 1.0d31</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
            <p>Improve the promptness and reliability of user avatars appearing in the timeline.</p>
            <p>Fix a bug detecting some JSON Feeds — those that use escaping on forward slashes in the text, such as http://curtclifton.net/feed.json</p>
            <p>Draw a white unread indicator in the timeline when the cell is selected and emphasized.</p>
            <p>Remove Error Log command from menu, since the Error Log won’t be until after 1.0.</p>
            <p>Use the git commit number as the build number in Info.plist. Use Curtis Herbert’s script: https://blog.curtisherbert.com/automated-build-numbers/</p>
            <p>Add Om Malik’s feed to the default list.</p>
            <p>Check /index.xml when finding a feed when there are no other leads.</p>
  
    						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 13:15:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d31.zip" sparkle:version="775" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d31" length="7224599" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

				<item>
          <title>Version 1.0d30</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
            <p>Show avatars in the timeline view at the right time — when viewing a folder, or when the articles in the timeline specify authors per article (as with Micro.blog timelines).</p>
            <p>Move favicons in the detail view to the right side. They’re shown when there’s no user avatar or feed icon.</p>
            <p>Fix avatar alignment in the detail view.</p>
            <p>Freeze the user agent as <code>Evergreen (macOS; RSS Reader; https://ranchero.com/evergreen/)</code>. (An iOS version would say iOS rather than macOS, but would be the same otherwise.)</p>
  
    						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 21:20:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d30.zip" sparkle:version="522" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d30" length="7214977" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

				<item>
          <title>Version 1.0d29</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
            <h4>Detail view</h4>
            <p>Feed icons and user avatars now go at the top right. (Except for favicons, which are still on the left. They should probably go to the right too.)</p>
            <p>The system gets feed icons from web page metadata now, when not specified in the feed.</p>
            
            <h4>Timeline view</h4>
            <p>Show the feed name when in a timeline that could show multiple feeds — such as when a folder is selected in the sidebar.</p>
            
            <h4>Misc.</h4>
            <p>Fixed a bug where favicons in the default location for a feed — /favicon.ico — wouldn’t get found.</p>
            <p>Make User-Agent of the form Evergreen/1.0d28 (Macintosh; RSS Reader; ranchero.com/evergreen/)</p>
            <p>Fix bug decoding &amp;#39; entities.</p>
            <p>Use Flying Meat’s JSON Feed in the feed directory.</p>
         
  						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 16:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d29.zip" sparkle:version="521" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d29" length="7200332" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

				<item>
          <title>Version 1.0d28</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
              <h4>Experimental version</h4>
            <p>Now shows feed and user avatars in the detail view, when they’re available in the feed. (Requires JSON Feed feeds, at least for now.)</p>
            <p>This meant making layout changes to the detail view. Feedback is, of course, very much welcome.</p>
            
            <p>(The code for building the detail view’s HTML is currently a total mess while we’re experimenting. Don’t look at it. Consider yourself warned.)</p>
        
  						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d28.zip" sparkle:version="520" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d28" length="7193574" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>
        
				<item>

            <title>Version 1.0d27</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
            <h4>Detail status bar</h4>
            <p>The link display now appears only during mouseover. Works much like Safari.</p>
            <p>There is no persistent display of the current permalink. We’ll see if we miss it or not.</p>
            
            <h4>Icons</h4>
            <p>Using a generic icon for feeds that don’t have a favicon. This icon may change.</p>
            
            <h4>Misc.</h4>
            <p>Futzed around with the Feed Directory UI.</p>
        
  						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 18:45:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d27.zip" sparkle:version="519" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d27" length="7185976" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

           <item>
            <title>Version 1.0d26</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
            <h4>New command - Mark Older as Read</h4>
            <p>This new command marks as read everything in the current timeline that’s older than the selected article.</p>
            <p>This command is also available as a keyboard shortcut: the o key. (Lowercase Oh, not zero.)</p>
            
            <h4>Share toolbar button</h4>
            <p>It works, sort-of. Has issues. But you can share things. Sort-of-ish.</p>
            
            <h4>Misc.</h4>
            <p>Fixed an infinite loop that could happen when going to next unread.</p>
            <p>The main sidebar and the sidebar in the Feed Directory now use standard folder icons for folders.</p>
  					<p>Fixed OPML export bug — the OPML is now valid.</p>
						<p>Fixed bug sizing the Keyboard Shortcuts window on a small screen.</p>
						<p>Made Mark as Starred command not doing anything (for now) — it was doing the wrong thing.</p>
						<p>Move Keyboard Shortcuts menu item to the Help menu.</p>
						<p>Use semantic markup in the Keyboard Shortcuts HTML. Courtesy of ePirat.</p>
						<p>Return to the normal app icon. Until next year.</p>
						<p>Validate unread counts on fetching articles without having to hit the database for the validation.</p>
						<p>Restore window size/position and splitview position in the Feeds Directory window between runs.</p>
						
						<h4>More info</h4>
						<p>You can always look at the <a href="https://github.com/brentsimmons/Evergreen/commits/master">recent commits on GitHub</a> for more details.</p>
						<p>And you can look at the <a href="https://github.com/brentsimmons/Evergreen/milestone/1">current milestone</a> to see what remains to be done.</p>
  						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 18:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d26.zip" sparkle:version="518" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d26" length="7330000" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

          <item>
            <title>Version 1.0d25</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            
            <h3>Warning: Re-runs</h3>
            <p>I fixed a couple bugs with how article database IDs are created. This will cause re-runs. Sorry about that! I am trying to avoid things like this, but it could happen again before we get to 1.0 alpha.</p>
            
            <h4>Keyboard Shortcuts</h4>
						<p>Open Window > Keyboard Shortcuts to see the list of keyboard shortcuts (shortcuts not otherwise in the menubar).</p>
						<p>The keyboard shortcuts listed all work — when either the sidebar or timeline has focus. (They don’t work yet when the detail view has focus.)</p>
						
						<h4>First Run</h4>
					  <p>Position and size the main window more nicely.</p>
					  <p>Edited the default feeds list slightly.</p>
						<p>Fixed bug where On My Mac group item title would be blank on first run.</p>
	
						<h4>Parsers</h4>
						<p>Parse authors and attachments in Atom feeds.</p>
						<p>Add support for multiple authors in Atom and RSS.</p>
						<p>In RSS feeds, detect when an author is really a URL or a name as opposed to an email address.</p>
							
						<h4>Misc.</h4>
						<p>Added link to Technotes in the Help menu. It goes to the Technotes index page in the GitHub repository.</p>
						<p>Refresh-all on startup (unless running a debug build).</p>
						
						<h4>More info</h4>
						<p>You can always look at the <a href="https://github.com/brentsimmons/Evergreen/commits/master">recent commits on GitHub</a> for more details.</p>
  						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 14:50:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d25.zip" sparkle:version="517" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d25" length="7330000" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Version 1.0d24</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            <h4>UI changes</h4>
						<p>Instead of an old-fashioned status bar — an app “chin” — the gear menu and refresh status appear at the bottom of the sidebar, and the current article‘s URL (or mouseover URL) appears at the bottom of the detail view.</p>
						<p>Feedback is welcome on this change. It might need reversing or refining. Or it might be fine as-is. Let me know what you think.</p>

						<h4>Performance</h4>
						<p>The time between clicking on a feed — or especially a folder — and when the articles appear in the timeline view has been drastically reduced. This was due to a number of changes. (Thanks to Instruments!)</p>
						<p>OPML importing was slow — now it’s borderline instantaneous, even with thousands of feeds.</p>
						<p>HTML metadata parsing is now cached and performed on a background thread.</p>

						<h4>Misc.</h4>
						<p>Detect and parse RSS feeds that lack an opening rss tag. (See https://www.natashatherobot.com/feed/ as an example.)</p>
						<p>When the home page of a feed isn’t known yet, base the favicon on the feed URL.</p>
						<p>Fix a memory leak that happened every time you added a feed.</p>
						<p>Removed signs of some features that won’t appear until 2.0. (I’ve been doing some punting. It hurts, but that’s how I know I’m doing it right.)</p>
						<p>Increased spacing in sidebar from small to medium.</p>
						<p>The smart feeds now appear in a Smart Feeds group in the sidebar.</p>

						<h4>More info</h4>
						<p>You can always look at the <a href="https://github.com/brentsimmons/Evergreen/commits/master">recent commits on GitHub</a> for more details.</p>
  						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 20:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d24.zip" sparkle:version="516" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d24" length="7289118" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

       <item>
            <title>Version 1.0d23</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Decorate the tree!</p>
  						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 5 Dec 2017 13:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d23.zip" sparkle:version="515" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d23" length="7306243" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

       <item>
            <title>Version 1.0d22</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Refresh all after importing OPML.</p>
            <p>Fetch unread counts from database at startup.</p>
            <p>Make resizing the timeline view marginally faster.</p>
            <p>Make the favicon downloading system use a little less memory.</p>
            <p>Read a newly-added feed immediately, instead of waiting for the next refresh-all.</p>
            <p>Use 38-pt-wide toolbar icons, a la Mail.</p>
            <p>Parse RSS 1.0 (RDF) feeds. Pinboard uses these (I couldn’t find them anywhere else).</p>
            <p>Make the window title-less. You can bring back the title using a <a href="https://github.com/brentsimmons/Evergreen/blob/master/Technotes/HiddenPrefs.md">hidden pref</a>.</p>
            <p>Save feed authors.</p>
            <p>Save article authors.</p>
            <p>Use updated @2x next-unread icon from Brad.</p>
            <p>Fix bug detecting feed type for Dr. Drang’s JSON Feed.</p>
            <p>Fix bug detecting Macworld’s RSS feed as an RSS feed. The feed doesn’t start with the standard XML header.</p>
            <p>Set user-agent on the detail view’s webview.</p>
						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 4 Dec 2017 13:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d22.zip" sparkle:version="514" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d22" length="7153185" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>
      
      <item>
            <title>Version 1.0d20</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Fixes several bugs with downloading and displaying favicons.</p>
						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 21:45:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d20.zip" sparkle:version="512" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d20" length="7110096" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

       <item>
            <title>Version 1.0d19</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            <p>The left-hand sidebar now shows favicons.</p>
            <p>The Feed Directory sidebar also shows favicons.</p>
            <p>Note: obvious missing thing is a default image for when there is no favicon. See <a href="https://github.com/brentsimmons/Evergreen/issues/208">https://github.com/brentsimmons/Evergreen/issues/208</a>.
						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 11:50:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d19.zip" sparkle:version="511" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d19" length="7068870" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Version 1.0d18</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Resuming distribution via Sparkle.</p>
						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2017 13:15:00 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d18.zip" sparkle:version="510" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d18" length="7041557" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

          <item>
            <title>Version 1.011</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            <p>First Evergreen release.</p>
						]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 15:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/Evergreen1.0d11.zip" sparkle:version="500" sparkle:shortVersionString="1.0d11" length="4659981" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.12</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
