<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>NetNewsWire Releases</title>
        <link>https://ranchero.com/downloads/netnewswire-release.xml</link>
        <description>Most recent NetNewsWire releases (not test builds). Well, we’re including test builds up until 5.0 ships, but after that it won’t be test builds.</description>
        <language>en</language>

				<item>
         <title>NetNewsWire 5.0.2</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
<p>The app movement monitor has been updated to handle quarantined apps and translocation.</p>

<p>Normally we wouldn’t have pushed out a new release for a single bug fix, but this one is important — we were getting false positives on app movement, which was affecting some users negatively.</p>
 							]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 11:20:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/brentsimmons/NetNewsWire/releases/download/mac-5.0.2/NetNewsWire5.0.2.zip" sparkle:version="2615" sparkle:shortVersionString="5.0.2" length="5082387" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.14.4</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

				<item>
         <title>NetNewsWire 5.0.1</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
<p>Crash fix: when the app is renamed or moved on disk while running, alert the user and quit the app. This prevents crashes that will happen due to renaming/moving. See Daniel Jalkut on <a href="https://red-sweater.com/blog/3508/app-movement-monitoring">App Movement Monitoring</a> for more info.</p>

<p>(Probably) fix a crashing bug having to do with a callback being called more than once, when it was designed to be called just once.</p>

<p>Sidebar: deleting an empty Feedbin folder no longer makes the sidebar non-responsive.</p>

<p>Timeline: update UI more quickly when a feed icon is downloaded.</p>

<p>Timeline: reload the timeline when show-feed-names is toggled. This fixes a bug where switching between a folder and a feed with the exact same list of articles to appear in the timeline would result in display glitches.</p>

<p>Timeline and article pane: make sure the link for an article isn’t an empty string.</p>

<p>Article pane: stop blocking links containing the string “feedburner” — there are legitimate cases where that string appears.</p>

<p>Article pane: handle figures and iframes as we do images, so they fit in the view.</p>

<p>Article pane: fix white flash on first article load while in Dark Mode.</p>

<p>Preferences > General: add checkbox to hide the unread count in the Dock.</p>

<p>Preferences > Accounts: Updated the UI when a Feedbin user with an expired trial creates an account in NetNewsWire.</p>

<p>RSS parser: Detect RDF (RSS 1.0) feeds that lack an XML header.</p>

<p>RSS parser: Parse Atom-style dates that are missing a T character in the middle.</p>

<p>RSS parser: check for bad permalinks more aggressively. If they don’t contain a / character, then do not consider them permalinks.</p>

<p>RSS parser: don’t let author/title overwrite item/title.</p>

<p>About window: add link to NetNewsWire website.</p>

<p>Feedbin syncing: fixed a bug where starred articles could appear as unread.</p>

<p>Microblog Mac app sharing: when it has to launch the app first, it waits a little longer before sending it content, which should fix a bug where sometimes you get no content in that case.</p>

<p>Enable the Open in Browser command only when a single article is selected.</p>

 							]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 13:40:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/brentsimmons/NetNewsWire/releases/download/mac-5.0.1/NetNewsWire5.0.1.zip" sparkle:version="2614" sparkle:shortVersionString="5.0.1" length="5095218" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.14.4</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

		<item>
         <title>NetNewsWire 5.0b6</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            	<p>Okay — one last beta! Pretty sure, at least.</p>
            	<p>Fixes a bug with undoing deleting feeds or folders. The sidebar wouldn’t update afterward to show that the feed is back. Now it does.</p>
            	<p>Opens preferences window in center of screen.</p>
           		<p>Centers main window on first launch.</p>
 							]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 18:50:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/brentsimmons/NetNewsWire/releases/download/mac-5.0b6/NetNewsWire5.0b6.zip" sparkle:version="2608" sparkle:shortVersionString="5.0b6" length="5174618" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.14.4</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

			<item>
         <title>NetNewsWire 5.0b4</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            	<p>Fixed a bug showing the unread count for the selected feed, smart feed, or folder.</p>
 							]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/NetNewsWire5.0b4.zip" sparkle:version="2606" sparkle:shortVersionString="5.0b4" length="5168358" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.14.4</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
