<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>NetNewsWire Releases</title>
        <link>https://ranchero.com/downloads/netnewswire-release.xml</link>
        <description>Most recent NetNewsWire releases (not test builds). Well, we’re including test builds up until 5.0 ships, but after that it won’t be test builds.</description>
        <language>en</language>

<item>
    <title>NetNewsWire 5.1.2</title>
    <description><![CDATA[
<p>Fixed a crashing bug in the timeline</p>
<p>Fixed a background color bug in dark mode in the timeline</p>
<p>Fixed a crashing bug updating the browser popup in Preferences</p>
<p>Feedbin: fixed bug where credentials couldn’t be updated</p>
<p>Feedly: fixed bug syncing feed name changes</p>
<p>Feedly: fixed a bug adding a feed to a Feedly collection that has a + in its name</p>
<p>On My Mac: increased performance downloading feeds in the On My Mac account</p>
    ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 11:25:00 -0700</pubDate>
    <enclosure url="https://github.com/Ranchero-Software/NetNewsWire/releases/download/mac-5.1.2/NetNewsWire5.1.2.zip" sparkle:version="3016" sparkle:shortVersionString="5.1.2" length="6583447" type="application/zip" />
    <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
</item>

<item>
	<title>NetNewsWire 5.1.1</title>
	<description><![CDATA[
<p>Fixed a crash handling a specific type of weird URL</p>
<p>Preferences: restored ability to set default RSS reader</p>
<p>Fixed bug where o key wouldn’t mark older as read</p>
<p>Fixed an Open System Preferences button in an alert that didn’t work</p>
<p>Fixed a possible hang when adding a feed to Feedly (and the feed isn’t found)</p>
<p>Fixed some UI issues to do with adding a Feedly account</p>
<p>Fixed contrast in footnotes indicator</p>
<p>Fixed bug where duplicate accounts (same username and service) could be made</p>
<p>Fixed bug where open in Safari in background might not open in the background</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 11:45:00 -0700</pubDate>
	<enclosure url="https://github.com/Ranchero-Software/NetNewsWire/releases/download/mac-5.1.1/NetNewsWire5.1.1.zip" sparkle:version="3012" sparkle:shortVersionString="5.1.1" length="6582076" type="application/zip" />
	<sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
</item>

<item>
	<title>NetNewsWire 5.1</title>
	<description><![CDATA[
<p>Changes since 5.0.4:</p>
<p>Feedly syncing</p>
<p>Reader view</p>
<p>Notifications (configure per feed in the Info window)</p>
<p>Multiple windows - File > New Window</p>
<p>View > Hide Read Feeds</p>
<p>View > Hide Read Articles (also a filter button above timeline for this)</p>
<p>Clean Up command (to immediately hide read articles when hide-read-articles is on)</p>
<p>Feeds view: remember expansion state between runs</p>
<p>Timeline: more compact rows (source and date on same line)</p>
<p>Timeline: sort menu on top</p>
<p>Timeline: swipe actions</p>
<p>Article view: shift-space scrolls backwards</p>
<p>Articles with non-ASCII URLs can now open in browser</p>
<p>Adding feeds with non-ASCII URLs now works</p>
<p>AppleScript: article now has a feed property</p>
<p>Hold down shift to temporarily toggle open-in-browser in background preference</p>
<p>Article > Mark Above as Read, Mark Below as Read</p>
<p>Preferences: Choose preferred browser (for viewing web pages)</p>
<p>Inspector: window title now matches name of thing being inspected</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 12:45:00 -0700</pubDate>
	<enclosure url="https://github.com/Ranchero-Software/NetNewsWire/releases/download/mac-5.1/NetNewsWire5.1.zip" sparkle:version="3007" sparkle:shortVersionString="5.1" length="6561360" type="application/zip" />
	<sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
</item>

	<item>
         <title>NetNewsWire 5.0.4</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
<p>Performance enhancement: fetching articles is faster and uses less memory</p>

<p>Changed the retention policy to match iOS</p>

<p>Feeds view: fixed bug where multiple sequential deletes could mess up the current selection index</p>

<p>Article view: dealt with Twitter change that caused Twitter embeds to get cut off</p>

<p>Article view: properly size emojis that are actually graphics (from Wordpress, for instance)</p>

<p>Article view: stop playing any audio if the window is closed</p>

<p>Article view: don’t let line lengths get too long</p>

<p>Article view: fixed display of BandCamp widgets</p>

<p>OPML export: use an accessory view instead of an intermediate sheet</p>

<p>Add Folder: disable Add Folder button when text field is empty</p>

<p>Feed icons: get more icons from Feedbin; get favicons from some tricky cases</p>

<p>Add Feed: now allows IPv6 literal URLs</p>

<p>Feed discovery: give less weight to feeds with the word “podcast” in them, because they’re probably not what we want</p>

<p>Refreshing: fixed bug where automatic refreshing might not happening after the computer wakes from sleep</p>

<p>Preferences > Accounts: Renamed “Create” account button to “Add Account”</p>

<p>Fixed bug where a Feedbin article could stay unread right after you select it</p>

<p>Fixed bug where folder names with double quotes would have the quotes replaced with the HTML entity for quote</p>

<p>When importing from NNW 3, the app now ignores script feeds (since we don’t have that feature yet)</p>

<p>Fixed bug where, right after initial launch, the spacebar might not work to go to next unread article</p>

<p>Pressing return now opens the selected article in your browser</p>
		]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 11:40:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/Ranchero-Software/NetNewsWire/releases/download/mac-5.0.4/NetNewsWire5.0.4.zip" sparkle:version="2622" sparkle:shortVersionString="5.0.4" length="5130054" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.14.4</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

	<item>
         <title>NetNewsWire 5.0.3</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
<p>Significantly enhanced performance during syncs and refreshes. Fetching articles from the database is also faster.</p>

<p>When running for the first time, and the user previously used NetNewsWire 3, it will automatically import NetNewsWire 3 subscriptions instead of the defaults for new users.</p>

<p>You can also import NetNewsWire 3 subscriptions via the new File > Import NNW3 Subscriptions… command.</p>

<p>Keyboard shortcuts: the 's' key toggles starred status. The 'r' and 'u' keys now both toggle read status (instead of setting read and unread status, respectively).</p>

<p>Articles view: articles where the feed icon is quite large would be slow to render — now they render as fast as other articles.</p>

<p>Articles view: a bug where keyboard shortcuts wouldn’t work after giving the articles view focus has been fixed.</p>

<p>Articles view: YouTube videos could end up small. Fixed.</p>

<p>Articles view: fixed a bug scaling images to fit in the view.</p>

<p>Fixed the space bar when running on Catalina. It wouldn’t advance to the next unread — now it will. (This was due to a change in JavaScript in Catalina.)</p>

<p>Fixed a crashing bug having to do with async database fetches for the timeline.</p>

<p>Feedbin syncing: fixed a bug where renaming a tag on the Feedbin site would result in feeds in NNW ending up at the top level.</p>

<p>Help menu: fixed the expired Slack link.</p>

 		]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/brentsimmons/NetNewsWire/releases/download/mac-5.0.3/NetNewsWire5.0.3.zip" sparkle:version="2618" sparkle:shortVersionString="5.0.3" length="5152201" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.14.4</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

				<item>
         <title>NetNewsWire 5.0.2</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
<p>The app movement monitor has been updated to handle quarantined apps and translocation.</p>

<p>Normally we wouldn’t have pushed out a new release for a single bug fix, but this one is important — we were getting false positives on app movement, which was affecting some users negatively.</p>
 							]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 11:20:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/brentsimmons/NetNewsWire/releases/download/mac-5.0.2/NetNewsWire5.0.2.zip" sparkle:version="2615" sparkle:shortVersionString="5.0.2" length="5082387" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.14.4</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

				<item>
         <title>NetNewsWire 5.0.1</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
<p>Crash fix: when the app is renamed or moved on disk while running, alert the user and quit the app. This prevents crashes that will happen due to renaming/moving. See Daniel Jalkut on <a href="https://red-sweater.com/blog/3508/app-movement-monitoring">App Movement Monitoring</a> for more info.</p>

<p>(Probably) fix a crashing bug having to do with a callback being called more than once, when it was designed to be called just once.</p>

<p>Sidebar: deleting an empty Feedbin folder no longer makes the sidebar non-responsive.</p>

<p>Timeline: update UI more quickly when a feed icon is downloaded.</p>

<p>Timeline: reload the timeline when show-feed-names is toggled. This fixes a bug where switching between a folder and a feed with the exact same list of articles to appear in the timeline would result in display glitches.</p>

<p>Timeline and article pane: make sure the link for an article isn’t an empty string.</p>

<p>Article pane: stop blocking links containing the string “feedburner” — there are legitimate cases where that string appears.</p>

<p>Article pane: handle figures and iframes as we do images, so they fit in the view.</p>

<p>Article pane: fix white flash on first article load while in Dark Mode.</p>

<p>Preferences > General: add checkbox to hide the unread count in the Dock.</p>

<p>Preferences > Accounts: Updated the UI when a Feedbin user with an expired trial creates an account in NetNewsWire.</p>

<p>RSS parser: Detect RDF (RSS 1.0) feeds that lack an XML header.</p>

<p>RSS parser: Parse Atom-style dates that are missing a T character in the middle.</p>

<p>RSS parser: check for bad permalinks more aggressively. If they don’t contain a / character, then do not consider them permalinks.</p>

<p>RSS parser: don’t let author/title overwrite item/title.</p>

<p>About window: add link to NetNewsWire website.</p>

<p>Feedbin syncing: fixed a bug where starred articles could appear as unread.</p>

<p>Microblog Mac app sharing: when it has to launch the app first, it waits a little longer before sending it content, which should fix a bug where sometimes you get no content in that case.</p>

<p>Enable the Open in Browser command only when a single article is selected.</p>

 							]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 13:40:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/brentsimmons/NetNewsWire/releases/download/mac-5.0.1/NetNewsWire5.0.1.zip" sparkle:version="2614" sparkle:shortVersionString="5.0.1" length="5095218" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.14.4</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

		<item>
         <title>NetNewsWire 5.0b6</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            	<p>Okay — one last beta! Pretty sure, at least.</p>
            	<p>Fixes a bug with undoing deleting feeds or folders. The sidebar wouldn’t update afterward to show that the feed is back. Now it does.</p>
            	<p>Opens preferences window in center of screen.</p>
           		<p>Centers main window on first launch.</p>
 							]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 18:50:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/brentsimmons/NetNewsWire/releases/download/mac-5.0b6/NetNewsWire5.0b6.zip" sparkle:version="2608" sparkle:shortVersionString="5.0b6" length="5174618" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.14.4</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

			<item>
         <title>NetNewsWire 5.0b4</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            	<p>Fixed a bug showing the unread count for the selected feed, smart feed, or folder.</p>
 							]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="https://ranchero.com/downloads/NetNewsWire5.0b4.zip" sparkle:version="2606" sparkle:shortVersionString="5.0b4" length="5168358" type="application/zip" />
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.14.4</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
